https://www.shawfest.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy - Shaw Festival Theatre
Privacy Policy - Shaw Festival Theatre
Privacy Policy
Annie McWhinnie and Kristi Frank backstage (The Horse and His Boy, 2019).
Shaw Festival TheatrePrivacy Policy
What
Over the course of our relationship, personal information collected may include your name, street and email addresses, phone and credit card numbers and purchase and donation history. Additional personal information such as names of family members, business addresses and special interests, may also be recorded for dedicated and long-term supporters of The Shaw.
When
Most of this information is collected when you request a brochure, buy tickets, make a donation, sign up for e-mail correspondence, enter our contests or fill out surveys.
Why
We need this information for billing purposes, tickets and tax receipt distribution, and to inform you about schedule changes, upcoming events or special offers. We may also use it to build a profile of our audience for marketing and fundraising initiatives or future programming.
Where
Only authorized personnel have access to your information. If we share it with an outside organization (such as a mailing house or professional research firm), they are bound by contract to the same strict privacy controls that we use ourselves and the information provided is for one-time use only. Information that you provide at our website during the secure connection is encrypted for security and transferred with no risk of being intercepted.
How
With your consent, we will send correspondence that we believe to be of interest to you. We try to contact all our ticket buyers at least once a year to obtain feedback, update our records and offer the opportunity to become more closely associated with The Shaw. Sometimes we may also share information regarding related cultural organizations or our sponsors. As a registered charitable organization, the Shaw Festival is exempt from the National Do Not Call List, we are however committed to ensuring that patrons and donors do not receive an unreasonable number of letters, phone calls or e-mails. We also assess new technology for protecting customer information on an ongoing basis.
For more information about PIPEDA (Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act) visit the website of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada privcom.gc.ca. For further information about the National Do Not Call list, please visit crtc.gc.ca and for US patrons donotcall.gov.
Communication preferences
If your information or preferences change, or if you no longer wish to receive communication from us, please let us know by calling 1-800-511-7429 or online here if you have an online account.
Mailing address:
